Guide to the Leo K. Bustad Papers 1912-2005
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 5: Audiovisual Materials
  - Subseries 5.4: Audiocassettes
    - Hocker second generation, undated (Folder 42)
    - "How are we going to feed all the people" vocation, undated (Folder 42)
    - Religious symposium, undated (Folder 42)
    - Dr. Kilgore animal rights, undated (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - Interview with Jerry Van Hoosier laboratory animals on "Meet with Mary Ellen", undated (Folder 42)
    - Do animals think, 1989 October 11 (Folder 42)
    - Dr. Carson session on pets in therapy, undated (Folder 42)
    - J. Starke, ?1990 (Folder 42)
    - Grant and Wagner on wobblers, undated (Folder 42)
    - Grant, 1978 January 03 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, ?1990 (Folder 42)
    - Sacher, 1979 June 28 (Folder 42)
    - Tom Clarkson, undated (Folder 42)
    - Dr. Penny, undated (Folder 42)
    - Smithcor interview with Dr. Lacroix, 1979 April 19 (Folder 42)
    - Vetrospect, 1977 September (Folder 42)
    - John B. Jess Chapel of the Air, undated (Folder 42)
    - Joe Snyder Reverence for Life "cosmetic surgery", 1981 May 25 (Folder 42)
    - 10th anniversary celebration University of Tennessee College of Veterinary Medicine, keynote address Leo K. Bustad, undated (Folder 42)
    - Leadership, undated (Folder 42)
    - J. Varth animal behavior problems, 1978 May 08 (Folder 42)
    - Calvin's lecture, 1978 May 14 (Folder 42)
    - Conversation with M. Johnston, undated (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - Biology of aging conference Dr. Comfort, Dr. J. Holland, 1977 August (Folder 42)
    - Institute of Human Nutrition, session #2 - "Nutrition and the Killer Diseases": Side A "Clinical Manifestation and Dietary Management" Edward D. Fries, MD; Side B "Hypertension in Children" Margaret M. Kilcoyne, MD, 1979 November 29 (Folder 42)
    - Ethics and values, 1983 January 07 (Folder 42)
    - Terry Fossum senior paper, undated (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - Bustad, Leo "koinonia=transforming friendship" or "we are called to be fishers of men more than keepers of the aquarium" 33 minutes, undated (Folder 42)
    - Karen's memorial, undated (Folder 42)
    - LKB "idealist vs. practical man" University of Idaho 1980 April 03; "who's afraid of pheremones", 1980 April 16 (Folder 42)
    - LKB talk on humaneness to 1st year student, 1979 November (Folder 42)
    - Material on pet-facillitated therapy, undated (Folder 42)
    - Institute of Human Nutrition, session #2 - "Nutrition and the Killer Diseases": Side A "Preparation of Low Salt Diets" Mamdene Nelson, MD, 1979 November 29 (Folder 42)
    - Institute of Human Nutrition, session #3 - Side A "Etiology" George F. Cahill, Jr., MD; Side B "Dietary Management and Prognosis" Edwin L. Bierman, MD, 1979 November 29 (Folder 42)
    - Institute of Human Nutrition, session #3 - Side A "Fiber as a Binding Agent" Robert A. Levine, MD; Side B "Exercise" Philip Felig, MD, 1979 November 29 (Folder 42)
    - Institute of Human Nutrition, session #3 - Side A "Pancreatic Transplant" Keith Reemtsma, MD, 1979 November 29 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, 1993 March 03 (Folder 42)
    - "1/20 W. Env. Symm.", undated (Folder 42)
    - "1 25 Viriods Mon", undated (Folder 42)
    - "Xmas", undated (Folder 42)
    - 1979 prayer breakfast (Folder 42)
    - Joni Eareckson tells her own inspirational story, 1976 (Folder 42)
    - ADL talk #1 M. Zegler, undated (Folder 42)
    - Biochem, 1992 September 04 (Folder 42)
    - "The Meaning of Persons" Dr. Paul Tournier, ?1980 (Folder 42)
    - Christmas in Christ Chapel "Christmass for the animals" (condensed version), 1989 (Folder 42)
    - K. Banks immunology, undated (Folder 42)
    - Wildlife diseases, undated (Folder 42)
    - Institute of Human Nutrition, session #2 - "Nutrition and the Killer Diseases": Side A "Animal Studies" Louis Tobian, MD; Side B "Human Studies" Lot B. Page, MD, 1979 November 29 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, 1993 April 07 (Folder 42)
    - Biochemistry, 1992 (Folder 42)
    - Polio, undated (Folder 42)
    - Biotechnology, 1992 September 24 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - 588…unidentified…up to 1950-1960, circa 1950-1960 (Folder 42)
    - Biochemistry, 1991 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - Biotech, 1992 September 16 (Folder 42)
    - Hb. st. prop., 1991 September 16 (Folder 42)
    - organize/systematic, 1992 October 15 (Folder 42)
    - Biotech, 1992 October 13 (Folder 42)
    - Trapping with Dr. Forett/cosmetic surgery, undated (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - Bio, 1992 July 01 (Folder 42)
    - Biochem, ?1992 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - Copy of original mystery - given at Pullman Presbyterian Church ? July 24, undated (Folder 42)
    - Aging Dr. Radostels tape, 1981 February 06 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified (Folder 42)
    - 1st year students "More Than Scholars", 1977 December (Folder 42)
    - Aging M. Kay, 1980 May 22 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - Brosen, Jan "Anorexia Neurosa and Bolima" Brj-80-2 55 minutes, undated (Folder 42)
    - LKB - PPP, undated (Folder 42)
    - Reverence for Life, 1982 April 15 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - Jissell Kyrkjabo Glade, 1987 July (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - Veterinary contribution to environmental aspects of nuclear technology R.O. McClellen, 1975 May 02 (Folder 42)
    - Listening, 1978 October 02 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - Religious emphasis week, undated (Folder 42)
    - Ethics, undated (Folder 42)
    - Scientific advisory committee, 1980 September (Folder 42)
    - Ethics, undated (Folder 42)
    - American nationalism NPR, undated (Folder 42)
    - Institute of Human Nutrition "Nutrition and the Killer Diseases", session #1: Side A "HDL Cholesterol as Negative Risk Factor" Basil Rifkind, MD; Side B "Early Feeding Patterns and Atheroscol." Charles J. Gluck, MD, 1979 November 29 (Folder 42)
    - Institute of Human Nutrition "Nutrition and the Killer Diseases", session #1: Side A "Epidemiology of Killer Diseases" David M. Berkson, MD; Side B "Dietary Fat and Atherosclerosis" Scott M. Grady, MD, 1979 November 29 (Folder 42)
    - "2-17 Mut.", undated (Folder 42)
    - Biochemistry, 1992 October (Folder 42)
    - Endangered Species RFL ? May 08, undated (Folder 42)
    - Ethics and values 1993 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, 1992 September 25 (Folder 42)
    - M. Goldman ES/PS/80, undated (Folder 42)
    - Finch, 1973 May 07 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, 1979 May 04 (Folder 42)
    - History of Kathy Quinn Tape II, undated (Folder 42)
    - Retirement by Ben Jonness, ?1984 (Folder 42)
    - Vaccine, 1992 November 19 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, ?1992 (Folder 42)
    - P-values stat, 1992 October 06 (Folder 42)
    - Parvovir idea, 1992 March 23 (Folder 42)
    - Hepatitis C, undated (Folder 42)
    - Biochem 563 1, 1992 September 10 (Folder 42)
    - 3261, undated (Folder 42)
    - 2/12 F Eclipse, undated (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, 1992 October 15 (Folder 42)
    - Biotechnology lecture 3, 1992 August 01 (Folder 42)
    - AbQuin 1958 for Smithcor, 1978 October 23 (Folder 42)
    - Parasitic, 1992 April 09 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, 1992 October 11 (Folder 42)
    - V.M., 1992 April 21 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - Papou Rep., 1993 March 08 (Folder 42)
    - 2/1 M V-Rep., 1992 February 23 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, 1992 October 16 (Folder 42)
    - Biotechnology, 1992 September 22 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, 1992 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, ?1992 (Folder 42)
    - Antibody, 1992 March 23 (Folder 42)
    - Biotechnology 1st lecture, undated (Folder 42)
    - Biotech., 1992 September 08 (Folder 42)
    - Rhabdo, Parvm, 1992 March 01 (Folder 42)
    - To Sunni F, undated (Folder 42)
    - Virology Friday, 1992 March 27 (Folder 42)
    - Test no. 3, 1992 August 29 (Folder 42)
    - Biochem, 1991 October 21 (Folder 42)
    - 2/5 F phase display Dunke, undated (Folder 42)
    - Len Sagan, undated (Folder 42)
    - Seminar nonhuman primate tumor, 1974 June 14 (Folder 42)
    - Fax on comp. psychopath and last par of fax on wolves and dogs, 1974 May 17 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - Fred Smithcors evolution of food, 1978 October 23 (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - Chapter 3, 1992 September 03 (Folder 42)
    - Prof Rollin, undated (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, 1992 April 30 (Folder 42)
    - Tat, 1992 October 08 (Folder 42)
    - 1/15 F:V.St 6-1 Na.Env, undated (Folder 42)
    - M. Johnston, undated (Folder 42)
    - LKB, undated (Folder 42)
    - Ser. Hansen et al, undated (Folder 42)
    - Brosen, Jan "Anorexia Neurosa and Bolima" 55 minutes, undated (Folder 42)
    - Side 1 Ery Kman and Clarkson Side 2 Sedgewick, undated (Folder 42)
    - Branen - Wed, Thurs, undated (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, ?1981 (Folder 42)
    - LKB 8/24/4, undated (Folder 42)
    - History Kathy Quinn, undated (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - Compassion, undated (Folder 42)
    - Ethics Harry Silverstein, 1981 February (Folder 42)
    - 1A/1B, undated (Folder 42)
    - 2A/2B, undated (Folder 42)
    - 4A/4B, undated (Folder 42)
    - 5A/5B, undated (Folder 42)
    - from Brad Peterson's tape on Reverence for Life horse racing, undated (Folder 42)
    - The Seeing Eye: Its Policies and Services, undated (Folder 42)
    - Brain lesion, undated (Folder 42)
    - Wildlife, undated (Folder 42)
    - Tune in the World with Ham Radio: Your Introduction to Morse Code, 1982 (Folder 42)
    - Genocide, undated (Folder 42)
    - Dr. Leo Bustad 64th Pacific Northwest District Kiwanis Convention Hanford School Richland, 1981 August 15 (Folder 42)
    - Chris Pasquinn, undated (Folder 42)
    - War and overpopluation, undated (Folder 42)
    - Dr. Bakey intro, 1983 August 04 (Folder 42)
    - People animal interactions, undated (Folder 42)
    - Ethics, 1986 September 25 (Folder 42)
    - Reverence for Life October 02, undated (Folder 42)
    - CAP orientation, undated (Folder 42)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 42)
    - Eric Peterson wolf and people PPP, 1988 December (Folder 43)
    - Dr. Leathers 200 + lab animal, undated (Folder 43)
    - Bustad lession 6 morse code, undated (Folder 43)
    - 5 Ad. mtg, undated (Folder 43)
    - Tape 4, undated (Folder 43)
    - Reverence for Life wildlife, undated (Folder 43)
    - Agriculture USA, undated (Folder 43)
    - Schweitzer, 1985 September 04 (Folder 43)
    - Ken Meyers platelets and cardiovascular disease, undated (Folder 43)
    - Tapes by Drs. Slater and Pictila of banquet in honor of Dr. Bustad, 1983 April (Folder 43)
    - Memo to Dr. Bustad from Gary Bryan, undated (Folder 43)
    - Maximum strength weight loss, undated (Folder 43)
    - Animals: human and nonhuman shared destiny conference, 1987 October 31 (Folder 43)
    - 2 letters LKB, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Royal artist dictation systems, undated (Folder 43)
    - Reverence for Life Holocaust, undated (Folder 43)
    - Exotic species Ed Womack Reverence for Life, undated (Folder 43)
    - Soren-Bernstein phone call, 1980 July 30 (Folder 43)
    - Finch, undated (Folder 43)
    - B. Rollin, 1986 September 09 (Folder 43)
    - Vegetarianism Reverence for Life, ?1986 (Folder 43)
    - Final wrap up by J. Montmarquet, ?1985 (Folder 43)
    - Report on workshops 1. by David Dean Radeley School 2. T. Rattency, undated (Folder 43)
    - David Dean Principal Raddeny School, undated (Folder 43)
    - End of talk by Argus Whyte/Kathy Quinn's presentation>coffee break>video>question time>impromptu dogs visiting prisons Marj. H-Price, undated (Folder 43)
    - Dr. Theron and Darlene Nelson Rally, undated (Folder 43)
    - Men and Molecules Side 1: A Tile at Genetic Ills Vasken Aposhia Side 2: Binding the Catalysts of Life Dr. John Huguenin, undated (Folder 43)
    - Animals: human and nonhuman shared destiny conference welcome: Kenneth Stevens, keynote address John B. Cobb, Jr., 1987 October 30 (Folder 43)
    - Incoming message, undated (Folder 43)
    - Wildlife symposium, undated (Folder 43)
    - Guidelines: animals in institutions, undated (Folder 43)
    - Guidelines: animals in institutions, undated (Folder 43)
    - Bagby tape side 1 only, undated (Folder 43)
    - Roger Pellen - to be typed, undated (Folder 43)
    - Animals: human and nonhuman a shared destiny symposium (2nd half) "Human Responsibility towards Animals" Kenneth Stephens (moderator), panel speakers: Virginia Knouse, Arthur Fisher, Dee Boersma, concluding remarks Michael Matriotti, 1987 October 31 (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, 1981 November (Folder 43)
    - PETE, undated (Folder 43)
    - Reverence for Life Vph499 10/22 animal in experimentation C. Alexander, undated (Folder 43)
    - Hooper-C.S. Lewis, undated (Folder 43)
    - Speakers Latham Symposium WSU, 1980 March (Folder 43)
    - "1st side continued on other side 1/20", undated (Folder 43)
    - Human-companion animal bond Linda Hines Mike McCulloch, undated (Folder 43)
    - Dr. Sisson, undated (Folder 43)
    - Tape 9 Matthew Fox, undated (Folder 43)
    - Reverence for Life 1. Margaret Davis, Liane Sperlich, undated (Folder 43)
    - PPP Kathy Slinker, 1980 April 10 (Folder 43)
    - Bustad Reverence for Life, 1983 May 01 (Folder 43)
    - Guelph Conference Tape 1 W. Bruce Douglas Jr., June 13 (Folder 43)
    - French quotes for Spink lecture, undated (Folder 43)
    - Grief, undated (Folder 43)
    - Ken Meyers platelets and cardiovascular disease, undated (Folder 43)
    - "What is a Pet?" kindergarten, undated (Folder 43)
    - "1st side only", 1978 September 13 (Folder 43)
    - Animals in research and teaching, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Reverence for Life, 1981 March 30 (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Alex Sheriff society and the adolescent, undated (Folder 43)
    - 2:20-3:15, 1979 September 07 (Folder 43)
    - Done, 1974 August 24 (Folder 43)
    - R. Clausen, 1991 October 09 (Folder 43)
    - "this side only", undated (Folder 43)
    - Spinks shorts, 1979 August 17 (Folder 43)
    - 2nd copy of Delta board meeting, undated (Folder 43)
    - K. Vaux dean's ethics, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Ethics of animals K. George September 28, undated (Folder 43)
    - On listening L. K. Bustad, undated (Folder 43)
    - Code tapes by Jerry Ziliak, 1983 (Folder 43)
    - Dr. Henson WSU equine research, undated (Folder 43)
    - Dean's talk on ethics and values, undated (Folder 43)
    - Bustad, Leo assistance animals Bu-L 89-1, undated (Folder 43)
    - Bustad, Leo human/animal bond - its significance/history/blessing Bu L 89-1, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Aging, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Reverence for Life, 1986 September 03 (Folder 43)
    - Animals in prison, undated (Folder 43)
    - Bustad, Leo and Henson, Keith "The Plight of the Handicapped - What to Do About It", undated (Folder 43)
    - 3A and 3B, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Animal rights, undated (Folder 43)
    - Animal law in Reverence for Life, 1988 November 09 (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Guinea pigs 15 minutes copy, undated (Folder 43)
    - Radiations December 16, undated (Folder 43)
    - 3 Rs are not enough, undated (Folder 43)
    - Reverence for Life Unitarian Church of the Palouse, undated (Folder 43)
    - Reverence for Life, 1985 September 18 (Folder 43)
    - Tuy's trip to Holden, undated (Folder 43)
    - Riding for handicapped (brief), undated (Folder 43)
    - "How Can We Feed All the People" L. Bustad, undated (Folder 43)
    - Surgery Betty Clark, undated (Folder 43)
    - Letters LKB, undated (Folder 43)
    - Ethics/human animal bond and art, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Short, undated (Folder 43)
    - Responsibilities of pet ownership, undated (Folder 43)
    - 6A and 6B, undated (Folder 43)
    - 7A and 7B, undated (Folder 43)
    - Theme "Aime-moi" "30" Fr. And Ang., undated (Folder 43)
    - J. Alexander-Danforth "Animal in Res.", undated (Folder 43)
    - Ethics discussion Leathers/Campbell 1984 January 09 (Folder 43)
    - "The American School Teacher and the Quest for Standards", undated (Folder 43)
    - Cats as pets (grade 3) copy 2, undated (Folder 43)
    - Reverence for Life Monica Messinger Amazon Rain Forest, undated (Folder 43)
    - Choosing a pet (grade 1) copy 1, undated (Folder 43)
    - Cats as pets (grade 3) copy 3, undated (Folder 43)
    - Dogs as pets, undated (Folder 43)
    - Little critters as pets (grade 2) copy 1, undated (Folder 43)
    - Non-pet animals (grade 5) copy 2, undated (Folder 43)
    - Responsibilities of pet ownership (grade 6) copy 3, undated (Folder 43)
    - Little critters as pets (grade 2) copy 3, undated (Folder 43)
    - Little critters as pets (grade 2) copy 2, undated (Folder 43)
    - Responsibilities of pet ownership (grade 6) copy 1, undated (Folder 43)
    - Responsibilities of pet ownership (grade 6) copy 2, undated (Folder 43)
    - Choosing a pet (grade 1) copy 2, undated (Folder 43)
    - Non-pet animals (grade 5) copy 1, undated (Folder 43)
    - Non-pet animals (grade 5) copy 3, undated (Folder 43)
    - Dogs as pets (grade 4) copy 1, undated (Folder 43)
    - Dogs as pets (grade 4) copy 2, undated (Folder 43)
    - Dogs as pets (grade 4) copy 2, undated (Folder 43)
    - 1988 Family Therapy Networrk Symposium (Folder 43)
    - "I and It" Oliver Sacks, MP, undated (Folder 43)
    - Charlyn Douglas History of HAB, 1990 August 29 (Folder 43)
    - Centennial tree planting, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - People-Pet Partnership, College of Veterinary Medicine, WSU, Pullman, WA 99164, undated (Folder 43)
    - Dr. Bonnie Beaver "Prevention and Treatment of Behavioral Problems in Cats", 1981 May 14 (Folder 43)
    - Bernie Rollin- "Problems with Pet-facilitated therapy" WSU, CUM, 1986 September (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - #3, 1986 November 16 (Folder 43)
    - Side 1 animals in entertainment Side 2 wildlife, undated (Folder 43)
    - Gary Marshall euthanasia, undated (Folder 43)
    - Ethics and values Bustand 11/10/2, undated (Folder 43)
    - Bethel for Latham, undated (Folder 43)
    - Garrison Keillor: hog slaughter, undated (Folder 43)
    - Downeast storytellers, undated (Folder 43)
    - Listen to the animals, listen to the wind Bill Van Noter, 1994 (Folder 43)
    - Novice theory part 2, undated (Folder 43)
    - FSN 5835-106-0421 C-60, undated (Folder 43)
    - Instruction Wang, undated (Folder 43)
    - Side 1 therapy on horseback - Stanford NARHA conference Side 2 backriding - Stanford, 1986 November 14 (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - AAOS, undated (Folder 43)
    - Men and Molecules: the unique American Chemical Society radio series: nutrition and the brain Dr. J. Fernstrom, undated (Folder 43)
    - Men and Molecules: the unique American Chemical Society radio series: screening for cancer agents Dr. B. Ames, undated (Folder 43)
    - Men and Molecules: the unique American Chemical Society radio series: cancer and the cell membrane Dr. R. Barnett, undated (Folder 43)
    - Cabinet meeting 12/13/8, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - 4-5-80 Evening side 2, ?1980 (Folder 43)
    - 4-5-80 afternoon sides 2 and 4, ?1980 (Folder 43)
    - 4-5-80 morning sides 2 and 4, ?1980 (Folder 43)
    - 4-5-80 afternoon sides 1 and 3, ?1980 (Folder 43)
    - 4-5-80 morning sides 1 and 3, ?1980 (Folder 43)
    - 4-5-80 evening sides 1 and 3, ?1980 (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Army history, undated (Folder 43)
    - My history, undated (Folder 43)
    - Art and importance of listening LKB, undated (Folder 43)
    - Abstract historical perspective, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Dr. D. Wood Thomas, 1980 November 14 (Folder 43)
    - Dr. Charles Leathers animal models research a and b, undated (Folder 43)
    - Jack Lein's sigma-xi presentation, undated (Folder 43)
    - Side 1 Dr. Pam Wagner-wobblers, side 2 Dr. Barrie Grant bone and heart, undated (Folder 43)
    - Reverence for Life, 1985 November 13 (Folder 43)
    - Computer assisted learning, 1982 October 21 (Folder 43)
    - Florida speech, undated (Folder 43)
    - Steve Blackwell 10/30/5 awareness/pain Janna Johnson, undated (Folder 43)
    - Cats as pets, undated (Folder 43)
    - Side A on wealth and poverty (Bustad, 1977), side b Paul Harvey on PPP, 1980 May 10 (Folder 43)
    - Guidelines: animals in institutions, undated (Folder 43)
    - CAP training Lou Lucas, 1986 September (Folder 43)
    - Human-pet bond conference parts 2 and 3, undated (Folder 43)
    - Dr. Robert Meier - PPP meeting, WSU Department of Sociology "prison populations", 1982 January 21 (Folder 43)
    - PEP volunteer orientation, undated (Folder 43)
    - Tribute to Dr. Small by Leo Bustad, undated (Folder 43)
    - "The Ethics of Animal Assisted Therapy" Delta Society conference part II, 1989 November (Folder 43)
    - "The Ethics of Animal Assisted Therapy" Delta Society conference part I, 1990 November (Folder 43)
    - Family 6/24/5, undated (Folder 43)
    - Men and Molecules: the unique American Chemical Society radio series: energy and industry A. Waterland, undated (Folder 43)
    - LKB letters, undated (Folder 43)
    - Letters for LKB, undated (Folder 43)
    - LKB's tribute to Dr. Small, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 43)
    - 1981 veterinary practice - pet loss and human emotion, undated (Folder 43)
    - Kathy George ethics Reverence for Life, undated (Folder 43)
    - Cindy Scoggins, undated (Folder 43)
    - Dr. Robert Meier - PPP meeting, WSU Department of Sociology "prison populations", 1982 November 21 (Folder 43)
    - Monday, undated (Folder 43)
    - Symposium on computer applications Dr. Lawrence Weed, 1982 October 13 (Folder 43)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 44)
    - History of Kathy Quinn, undated (Folder 44)
    - Bustad, 1972 (Folder 44)
    - Animal pain/animal awareness, undated (Folder 44)
    - Bloopers, undated (Folder 44)
    - Dean's copy Rollins ethics, undated (Folder 44)
    - Ethics discussion in microteaching, undated (Folder 44)
    - Colson, Charles and Hughs, Harld Chapel, Princeton University, 1975 December 14 (Folder 44)
    - Reverence for Life for Joe Snyder, 1981 February 10 (Folder 44)
    - Tape 3 side 1 questions and answers people-pet therapy, side 2 Dr. Alan Beck, undated (Folder 44)
    - Sitting vs. jogging LKB, 1983 January (Folder 44)
    - Unidentified, undated (Folder 44)
    - Tape 1 side 1 People Pet Partnership/side 2 Dr. Beck, Dr. McCullock, undated (Folder 44)
    - Reverence for Life vegetarianism, undated (Folder 44)
    - Reverence for Life, undated (Folder 44)
    - 1st side Wildlife Desert Symposium - intro and keynote by Gorham and Dieterich, 2nd side Weiland and Samuels, 1978 March 20 (Folder 44)